Adejare Taiwo

Lagos, Nigeria



emmanueladejare457@gmail.com



+2347085496237



linkedin.com/in/adejare-taiwo-360956197

Summary

Adejare Taiwo is a passionate young Software Developer (Backend) with proficient knowledge and experience from my previous challenges, HNG internship(3-month intense software development training) as one of the finalists and hands-on experience using Backend language(Nodejs[Express and XpresserJs], PHP(Laravel) to create and implement software applications. My dream is to be part of the team to learn and build the next big software that will help the tech world at large.

Experience



Software Developer

Paymyrent.ng Mar 2021 - Present (6 months +)



Back End Developer

PixelsHub Technologies Aug 2020 - Present (1 year 1 month +)

Software Developer Intern

Paymyrent.ng Jan 2020 - Present (1 year 8 months +)

Back End Developer

ProDevs Jan 2021 - Aug 2021 (8 months)

Back End Developer

Flux Technology Africa Aug 2020 - Dec 2020 (5 months)

Back End Developer

HNG Internship May 2020 - Aug 2020 (4 months)

Student and Junior web developer

Self Employed Feb 2020 - May 2020 (4 months)

■ Backend Web developer Instructor

Swap Space Systems Ltd Oct 2019 - Jan 2020 (4 months)

Education

University of Lagos

Bachelor's degree, Mathematics and Computer Science Nov 2019 - Present

Christ the Redeemer Secondary School

High School Diploma, Science 2014 - 2017

Licenses & Certifications

- **Web Development** Swap Space Systems Ltd
- Ship Programming Language Sololearn #1059-14583241
- introduction to Programming Using HTML and CSS Udemy UC-8YVLLSBG
- Introduction to Programming Using HTML Sololearn #1014-14583241
- **Web development** Udemy

Skills

PHP • Node.js • MySQL • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • HTML • JavaScript • Linux • Vagrant (Software) • Laravel • PhpMyAdmin

Honors & Awards

HNG Internship Finalist - Hotels.ng Sep 2020